Photo Good morning friends Friends, today's
video is by Arvind C Janata and in a video in which
we are finalizing the financial results in the morning
and q4202 today's topic is
that ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company Limited
Hello friends, in seconds ICICI
Lombard General Insurance
declared its results Friends,
without wasting time let's add Twitter Flickr
First of all what to see Player
of the festival is 31st March
after 20 minutes now subscribe to
subscribe and whether the quarter of perfect
subscribes or not when we
do it Friends, now the time has come,
he said that only operating profit
operating expenses is a separate item
and in that if these are
weak then it has been added later so
friends see this if this is a general insurance
company that means this will be the receiver of a commission
Friends, then this is a completely different type of work,
50 subscribe like this
to laptop and in that
I am working from office home and vice versa, more than 150
PM he collected heading
from this last quarter final  Z
that compared to the previous quarter almost every
quarter current affairs is a
little bit bigger than that and there is an increase in unpleasant income, there is increase in
hair growth, right, that
means the thing will be considered positive,
if we compare it with the last quarter of last year, then there is an
increase in that too and if there is a lot of
extension valuation then that will
also be considered positive and according to this result,
set it at the lowest at 90 in the result,
robbers
are a perfect channel, right now you people know
that the insurance company ignores and appoints
them, they have to pay commission, right,
their diabetes, this is the case of the Yagya
center's yoga profit operating profit,
friends now school operating profit
09870807070 means it is 2008
that he has come to his wife's house, compare to the
country, due to which positive profit is increasing
and best friend profit operating
profit for the quarter and this is all
combined
and of premium and total income has been made
moral quickly from that to meet the expenses in it
and by adding all this, profit
loss or profit has been made from that
360 perfect in the last quarter was 108
and west so it has decreased a little, it has
decreased a little, so what will happen in this,
friends, provisions have been carried, there will be a quarter
inch issue, it can happen due to that also,
not a major difference, if we
compare the latter under-20 with last year, then there is an
increase in it, it will go positive, now
in the skin problem, Twenty-20 on the
job, you were till 2011 in the previous quarter, there has been a slight
decrease in this also, I pray that
those people can understand that according to last year,
Uddhav will go, now the company had given
dividend of the last share, the
world, but in this business, no
limit has been released, it was perfect and the price was
2.5 in March last year, compared to that, it is
birthday, that means there has
not been much duty as per positive profit, that is
not the need of America, you all should subscribe to all this
and March 20th is in the to-do list,
sexy blue picture will be called, so we will
see one point two,
according to the previous quarter, this line has reached the maximum, that
means  There is not that big difference but the
complete last quarter of the previous year
₹1 100 friends, so all these friends are
not result based,
I just get messages, we
change the direction of birth, they have told till now
that the return online average means it will
reach 28%, if it is in 20% then it is a
little less than 21.35%
return on equity and oy give,
according to the video, it is positive, so the problem is a little bit, the
point has not been reached,
Ram Ram, when has the profit been made, subscribe
button on your lips, Reddy, these things were to be
shown to the people and because of this,
now we will see the effect of these,
we should see on the chart, people have
started a new system from today in the afternoon, you
for final properly and if we then the
resistance point in it is 354 323 506 and the
point is coming to 1512 and subscribe 12906, we
will see tomorrow how it reacts, tomorrow the
market should subscribe friends,
I have posted on Telegram  It will be updated, if
this point is caused then what is the syllable
and if the checkpoint is caused then
I have updated for both of them in telegraph, so
red, in this video we
use vitamins and if you have not subscribed to the channel then
if you have not subscribed to the channel then
subscribe to this video channel
and press the bell icon so that
you will get notifications of upcoming videos immediately on your mobile so that
no one misses
and you do not miss the video reddy and do not
forget to like share subscribe do
not forget to comment if you need any details then
we are for you
said that home Aditya Raj friends ok run is that
good article goodbye take care
send you thank you very much friends
Ajay